Your
[Music]
You always want to give your loved ones all the
best things in life, be it
your child's education,
holidays
or a better lifestyle for the family,
you ensure that your loved ones
get happiness and peace.
But as we all know, life is
full of uncertainties. Rising inflation,
future medical expenses and taxes can
further reduce your income. Therefore, you
need a plan that gives you
guaranteed returns in the form of regular income and
helps you meet the challenges of life.
Presenting ICICI Prudential Guaranteed
Income for Tomorrow Long Term, a plan
that gives you
tax-free guaranteed income as per your needs.
You can avail many benefits
like
life insurance cover for the entire policy term including the income period.
Guaranteed income to achieve your goals.
Tax benefits on premiums paid and benefits received. ICICI Prudential
Guaranteed Income for Tomorrow Long Term
comes with two options. Let's explore these options.
Understand in detail Income Option Saathiya
Pay premium for 10 years and choose to
get guaranteed income for 15 years, 2025 or 30 years and get
110% back Income Option
Saathiya Pay premium for 10 years and get 110% back Income Option Saathiya Pay premium for 15 years and get 110% back In
reality, by choosing to get guaranteed income till this year,
you get back 110% of the total premium paid along with your previous income.
You can also
decide to take the income annually or monthly as per your needs. Moreover, with the
help of Since Date feature, you
can choose any special guest of your choice to get guaranteed income. No matter how many ups and downs
in life,
you can always plan for life.
So what are you waiting for?
Enjoy every small and big moment with your loved ones
and
fulfil your dreams along with your responsibilities ICICI
Prudential Guaranteed Income Tomorrow
Long-term Goals Ajay Ko
Kar Do Kar
Do
[Music]